35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
35 millimeter slides
2.1.5.1
Marist College
  Box 1582
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Tibet, 1949; 1 (Box 1582)
    - [Man in Tibet carrying a yak skin boat], 1
    - [Tibetan monks carrying flour (?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas (left) and Lowell Thomas Jr. (right) with others in the mountains of Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (left) and Lowell Thomas (right) standing in front of Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 4
    - [Five Tibetan monks], 5
    - [Group of Tibetan people in front of Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 6
    - [Dalai Lama in Tibet], 7
    - [Two Tibetan women standing outside of a building], 8
    - [Man selling goods in Tibet], 9
    - [Herd of yak in Tibet], 10
    - [Tibetan statue of a warrior monkey(?)], 11
    - [Herd of yak in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving something from a Tibetan man], 13
  - Tibet, 1949; 2 (Box 1582)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two Tibetan locals], 1
    - [Line of donkeys carrying goods in Tibet], 2
    - [Potala Palace, Lhasa, Tibet], 3
    - [Monks at the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 4
    - [Mountains of Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan man walking towards a city, 6
    - [Top of Potala Palace in Tibet], 7
    - [City in Tibet], 8
    - [Sprawling city in TIbet], 9
    - [Two Tibetan children on a dirt road in front of a Tibetan city], 10
    - [Tibetan man looking out at the river], 11
    - [Person in Tibet holding a puppy], 12
    - [Mountains in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan monks at the Potala Plance in Lhasa, Tibet], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing with monks in Tibet], 15
    - [Herd of yak in Tibet], 16
    - [Group of people in a yak skin boat in Tibet], 17
    - [Mountains and ocean in Tibet], 18
    - [Two people looking at a stone building in Tibet], 19
    - [A small temple in Tibet], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas surrounded by horses in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 3 (Box 1582)
    - [People walking towards a mountain with a building on top in Tibet], 1
    - [Tibetan worker carrying wheat], 2
    - Tibetan people standing outside a stone wall], 3
    - [Tibetan person leaning on a stone building], 4
    - [Monks at the Potala Palance in Lhasa, Tibet], 5
    - [Snowly mountains of Tibet], 6
    - [Riding donkeys on a dirt road towards the mountains in Tibet], 7
    - [Snowy mountains in Tibet], 8
    - [Snow on the mountains of Tibet], 9
    - [Transporting a donkey in a yak skin boat in Tibet], 10
    - [Sunset over the Tibet mountains], 11
    - [Stopping for the donkeys to take a break on their journey towards the mountains in Tibet], 12
    - [Painting of Buddha in Tibet], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving a sash from a Tibetan man], 14
    - [Donkeys swimming in a river in Tibet], 15
    - [Herd of yak walking along the shore], 16
    - [Yak carrying supplies in Tibet], 17
    - [Donkey carrying CBS box with Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) holding up a banner for "Lodwick School of Aeronautics" in Tibet, 18
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. holding a sign for "Lodwick School of Aeronautics" in Tibet], 19
    - [Tibetan man riding a donkey], 20
    - [Two children standing on a dirt road in front of a city in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 4 (Box 1582)
    - [Unloading supplies in Tibet], 1
    - [Tibetan man rowing in a yak skin boat], 2
    - [Group of Tibetan people pushing a yak skin boat into the river], 3
    - [Donkey caravan in Tibet], 4
    - [Tibetan man leading the donkeys through water in Tibet], 5
    - [Yak caravan in Tibet], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas's group in Tibet], 7
    - [On top of a stone fort (?) in Tibet], 8
    - [On a horse looking at the mountains in Tibet], 9
    - [People passing through an ornate gate in Tibet], 10
    - [Stone building in Tibet], 11
    - [Group of native people in Tibet], 12
    - [Painting of a man and a tiger in Tibet], 13
    - [Rope over a river in Tibet], 14
    - [Tibetan man], 15
    - [Packing the donkey caravan in Tibet], 16
    - [Tibetan person riding a donkey in the caravan], 17
    - [Donkey caravan walking through water in Tibet], 18
    - [After unpacking the supplies from the donkeys], 19
    - [Tibetan person rowing in the yak skin boat], 20
    - [Yak caravan in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 5 (Box 1582)
    - [Stone building on top of a large rock in Tibet], 1
    - [Donkey caravan in Tibet], 2
    - [Man riding a Donkey in a caravan in Tibet], 3
    - [Yak skin boats propped up on oars in Tibet], 4
    - [Tibetan man sitting outside], 5
    - [Mountains and river in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan family], 7
    - [Rapids in a river in Tibet], 8
    - [Tibetan woman holding pottery], 9
    - [Tibetan monk behind an elephant statue], 10
    - [Caravan in Tibet], 11
    - [Donkey caravan walking through the river], 12
    - [Two men watching Tibetan women weave thread], 13
    - [Men riding on horses in Tibet], 14
    - [Men looking at a machine (?) in Tibet]], 15
    - [A crowd of people gathered in Tibet], 16
    - [Tibetan woman weaving thread], 17
    - [Tibetan women spooling thread], 18
    - [Tibetan women outside a clay (?) building], 19
    - [Man sitting in a field of flowers in Tibet], 20
    - [People surrounding a tent in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 6 (Box 1582)
    - [Caravan in Tibet], 1
    - [A group of men on horses in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan woman milking a goat], 3
    - [Tibetan men playing instruments], 4
    - [Tibetan children playing (?) while a crowd watches], 5
    - [Two Tibetan children fighting], 6
    - [Tibetan woman], 7
    - [Forest landscape in Tibet], 8
    - [Tibetan painting. Caption: "Khayyam, if you are intoxicated with wine, be glad you are sitting with one beautiful like the moon. Be happy. As the end of all things is non-existence. Assume that you are not and be happy that you still exist"], 9
    - [Tibetan workers shovelling hay], 10
    - [Men talking in Tibet], 11
    - [Two men sitting on a rug in Tibet], 12
    - [Two men sitting on a rug in Tibet], 13
    - [Men talking in Tibet], 14
    - [Crowd gathered in Tibet to watch men sparring (?)], 15
    - [Tibetan man picking up something from off the ground while riding a horse], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a man speaking in a tent in Tibet], 17
    - [Two men in Tibet sitting outside holding pouches], 18
    - [Tibetan man riding on a horse], 19
    - [Group of Tibetans gathered around to watch a sparring match], 20
    - [Group of men in Tibet on horses], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 7 (Box 1582)
    - [Group of Tibetan people with an ox], 1
    - [Fields and mountains in Tibet], 2
    - [People standing around yak skin boats in Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas taking photographs in Tibet], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas filling his canteen at a natural waterfall in Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan man sitting by flowers], 6
    - [River in the mountains of Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan men loading CBS equipment onto a donkey], 8
    - [Donkey caravan going up a rocky mountain], 9
    - [Tibetan family air drying yak skin boats], 10
    - [Line of Tibetan people carrying sticks on their backs], 11
    - [Tibetan people walking the streets of a city in Tibet], 12
    - [Tibetans unloading yak skin boats], 13
    - [Tibetan people sitting on the bank of a small pond], 14
    - [A Tibetan town], 15
    - [Two Tibetan women standing outside of a building], 16
    - [Two women talking outside of a building in Tibet], 17
    - [Donkey caravan walking through the mountains], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and three Tibetan monks (?) standing in front of the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 19
    - [Tibetan man walking towards a building with cloth (prayer flags?) tied to it], 20
    - [Donkey caravan going over a mountain in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 8 (Box 1582)
    - [Donkey caravan traveling through a valley in Tibet], 1
    - [Lowell and two men in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan man with a fish], 3
    - [Tibetan man kneeling down in the river], 4
    - [Herd of oxen (yak?) in Tibet], 5
    - [Herd of oxen (yak?) in the distance in Tibet], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) and others on a grassy mountain in Tibet], 7
    - [On top of a cloudly mountain in Tibet], 8
    - [Man with two horses on top of a mountain in Tibet], 9
    - [Open field with a grazing ox in Tibet], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas with three Tibetan men], 11
    - [Ornate architecture of a building in Tibet], 12
    - [Tibetan mountains], 13
    - [Wildflowers and a running stream in the mountains of Tibet], 14
    - [Cloudy mountain in Tibet], 15
    - [Tibetan men looking at a river from a mountaintop in Tibet], 16
    - [Two Tibetan men standing on top of a mountain], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and a Tibetan man standing in front of flowers], 18
    - [Supplies for journeying through Tibet], 19
    - [Tibetan man], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 9 (Box 1582)
    - [Family walking through the mountains of Tibet], 1
    - [Two men standing in front of four mountain shrines (?) in Tibet], 2
    - [Donkeys swimming through a river in Tibet], 3
    - [Horses and cattle grazing in the mountains of Tibet], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) looking down at a house from a mountain ], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and his caravan taking a break on their way through the mountains of Tibet], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) and a group of Tibetans at the top of a mountain in Tibet], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and four Tibetans outside of a city (?) wall], 8
    - [Small stream running through the mountains of Tibet], 9
    - [An ox (yak?) grazing in a valley in Tibet], 10
    - [Two oxen (yak?) grazing in Tibet], 11
    - [Caravan going up a mountain in Tibet], 12
    - [Donkey caravan walking through a forest in the mountains of Tibet], 13
    - [Dragon (?) statue in Tibet], 14
    - [Donkey caravan going through a mountain forest in Tibet], 15
    - [Two men riding horses through the mountains of Tibet], 16
    - [Tibetan monks (?) behind a wall of flowers], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) and another man on donkeys in Tibet], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas eating with three Tibetan men], 19
    - [Tibetan people standing outside a large building (a temple?)], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 10 (Box 1582)
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing to something from atop his donkey in the mountains of Tibet], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas inspecting the mountain flora in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan officer], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas leading the donkey caravan past a small house in Tibet], 4
    - [Monks walking on a dirt path in Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan man sitting on a rock in Tibet], 6
    - [Three men travelling with Lowell Thomas through the mountains], 7
    - [Tibetan soldiers], 8
    - [Tibetan soldiers lined up], 9
    - [Tibetan man sitting by a stream with his dog], 10
    - [Caravan traveling along the misty mountains of Tibet], 11
    - [Two children in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and a Tibetan man looking at a document], 13
    - [Tibetan officer and locals], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) sitting with three Tibetan people], 15
    - [Tibetan people in costume], 16
    - [Two Tibetan people], 17
    - [Line of Tibetan monks (?)], 18
    - [Mountain pathway in Tibet], 19
    - [Three Tibetan people sitting on rocks], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 11 (Box 1582)
    - [Tibetan family], 1
    - [Marketplace in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan monks walking through town], 3
    - [A Tibetan officer], 4
    - [Tibetan monks and officers walking through the streets of a city in Tibet], 5
    - [Monks in the streets of city in Tibet], 6
    - [Monks and others walking to the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 7
    - [People at the potala Palace(?)], 8
    - [Line of Tibetan people marching], 9
    - [Tibetan people sitting on the bank of a small pond], 10
    - [Monks in the Potala Palace (?)], 11
    - [Two people talking in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas eating with three Tibetan monks (?)], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas with a handful of berries in Tibet], 14
    - [Crowd of people gathered around three Tibetan people in white], 15
    - [Four Tibetan men in red], 16
    - [Donkey caravan on the mountains of Tibet], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas showing something to a Tibetan local], 18
    - [A man and woman], 19
    - [The mountains of Tibet], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 12 (Box 1582)
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at papers in Tibet], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing a Tibetan man], 2
    - [House in Tibet], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing a man in Tibet], 4
    - Lowell Thomas interviewing people in a busy square in Tibet], 5
    - [Two Tibetan monks], 6
    - [Tibetan woman holding a golden pitcher], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing a man in Tibet], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and two Tibetan monks in front of the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. wearing one of the monk's hats], 10
    - [Top of the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 11
    - [Tibetan people in a square], 12
    - [People performing for a crowd in Tibet], 13
    - [Mountains in Tibet], 14
    - [A house (apartment?) in Tibet], 15
    - [Man and woman standing in front of mountains in Tibet], 16
    - [People standing in front of a house in Tibet], 17
    - [Monks in Tibet], 18
    - [Performers in Tibet], 19
    - [Leading the donkey caravan through the water], 20
    - [Tibetan monks], 21
    - [Marketplace (?) in Tibet], 22
    - [Horses and riders traveling along a mountain path in Tibet], 23
    - [Performance area in Tibet], 24
  - Tibet, 1949; 13 (Box 1582)
    - [Array of goods sold at a Tibetan marketplace], 1
    - [Five people standing in front of the Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 2
    - [Ornate altar (?) in the Potala Palace], 3
    - [Monks outside a gate in Tibet], 4
    - [Two Tibetan women holding pottery and grain (?)], 5
    - [Altar in Potala Palace (?), Tibet], 6
    - [The Potala Palace in Lhasa, Tibet], 7
    - [Temple (?) at the Potala Palace (?)], 8
    - [Tibetan person on a horse], 9
    - [The young Tibetan Dalai Lama], 10
    - [The young Dalai Lama in Tibet], 11
    - [Monks bowing in Tibet], 12
    - [Tibetan people riding on horses], 13
    - [A large group of Tibetan people], 14
    - [Looking up at the Potala Palace (?)], 15
    - [Tibetan people passing through an archway in Tibet], 16
    - [Ornate archway in Tibet], 17
    - [The Dalai Lama sitting among flowers in Tibet], 18
    - [Tibetan people sitting outside a building], 19
    - [Six Tibetan monks], 20
    - [Four Tibetan monks], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 14 (Box 1582)
    - [Tibetan people playing a game (?)], 1
    - [Side of the Potala Palace (?)], 2
    - [Gold statue of Buddha (?) at the Potala Palace (?)], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a young Tibetan monk], 4
    - [Inside of the Potala Palace (?)], 5
    - [Four monks in Tibet], 6
    - [The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 7
    - [Three monks in Tibet], 8
    - [A Tibetan with his dog], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. talking with monks in Tibet], 10
    - [Stone shrine in Tibet], 11
    - [Performance tent in Tibet], 12
    - [Camp set up outside a walled town in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan people on the banks of a river in Tibet], 14
    - [Tibetan people riding on horses], 15
    - [Two Tibetan men with supplies next to stone wall], 16
    - [Tibetan people crossing a river with a caravan of donkies], 17
    - [Tibetan caravan on dirt road at the side of a river], 18
    - [Tibetan village on the side of a hill], 19
    - [Tibetan people with donkies carrying their supplies], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 15 (Box 1582)
    - [Tibetan people outside of their village], 1
    - [Crowded street in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan people in their village], 3
    - [Tibetan family dressed in robes], 4
    - [Tibetan person with their donkey on the bank of a river in Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan people on the bank of a river in Tibet], 6
    - [View of Tibetan village from a distance], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with a Tibetan person in Tibet], 8
    - [Tibetan people dressed in fancy robes], 9
    - [Tibetan monks], 10
    - [Tibetan artifacts on table], 11
    - [Two Tibetan monks], 12
    - [Tibetan people on the bank of a river in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan people holding sacks, Tibetan man dressed in colorful robes, shaking hands with Lowell Thomas], 14
    - [Tibetan monk standing outside of a Tibetan village], 15
    - [Tibetan man rowing, box marked as "CBS"], 16
    - [Tibetan artwork on stone wall], 17
    - [Tibetan man on a boat in Tibet], 18
    - [Tibetan monk], 19
    - [Tibetan people on river in Tibet], 20
    - [Tibetan people on side of a river], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 16 (Box 1582)
    - [Tibetan people dressed in colorful robes outside of a Tibetan palace], 1
    - [Tibetan village by mountain side], 2
    - [Tibetan people working on boats by riverside], 3
    - [Tibetan caravan outside of a Tibetan village located near mountainside], 4
    - [Tibetan people riding on horses on dirt road in Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan people working on boats by riverside], 6
    - [Pile of rocks in Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan man walking by a Tibetan building], 8
    - [Two Tibetan people with horse, just reaching land after crossing a river in Tibet], 9
    - [Two Tibetan people with horse, just reaching land after crossing a river in Tibet], 10
    - [Tibetan person rowing a boat on a river in Tibet], 11
    - [Tibetan family standing outside of a Tibetan building], 12
    - [Tibetan monks with Lowell Thomas, Jr. in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan person rowing a boat on a river in Tibet], 14
    - [Tibetan woman standing outside of a stone wall in Tibet], 15
    - [Tibetan artwork], 16
    - [Tibetan man and river], 17
    - [Tibetan person in a river in Tibet], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas with Tibetan monk], 19
    - [Tibetan village by a river], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. holding a carved stone in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 17 (Box 1582)
    - [Tibetan monks and Lowell Thomas (or Lowell Thomas, Jr.?) looking over bridge side at village], 1
    - [Tibetan people by rafts near a river in Tibet], 2
    - [Tibetan monks outside of Tibetan building], 3
    - [Tibetan people standing in a river in Tibet], 4
    - [Tibetan caravan on banks of river in Tibet], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. and view of river and mountains in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan people riding on horses in a field in Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan people outside of a walled-in village], 8
    - [Street in a Tibetan village], 9
    - [Tibetan caravan on a dirt road by the side of a river in Tibet], 10
    - [Tibetan caravan riding through fields surrounded by mountains in Tibet], 11
    - [Tibetan man with horse], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. sitting on a rock in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan caravan riding up a mountainous road], 14
    - [Tibetan people carrying supplies outside of a walled-in Tibetan village], 15
    - [Two men and Lowell Thomas, Jr. standing on flat land, mountains in distance; in Tibet], 16
    - [Tibetan people giving a performance in Tibet], 17
    - [Tibetan village by the side of a mountain], 18
    - [Tibetan caravan riding up mountainside], 19
    - [Tibetan monks], 20
    - [Tibetan caravan travelling across flat land, mountains in the distance; in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 18 (Box 1582)
    - [The Potala Palace in Tibet], 1
    - [Ruined city in Tibet, Caravan sitting outside], 2
    - [Tibetan oxen (yak?) in field], 3
    - [Tibetan man sitting cross-legged in a field, with a gun over his shoulder, in Tibet], 4
    - [Young Tibetan monks in a village in Tibet], 5
    - [Tibetan soldiers in Tibet], 6
    - [Man standing near a rock wall, snowcapped mountain in the background], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on a rock in Tibet], 8
    - [Tibetan people at a village market in Tibet], 9
    - [Tibetan people standing outside of a Tibetan building], 10
    - [The Potala Palace in the distance], 11
    - [On top of a mountain in Tibet], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas conversing with a Tibetan person outside of a Tibetan village], 13
    - [Snowcapped mountain in Tibet], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas reading a piece of parchment with a Tibetan person in Tibet], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. standing in front of snowcapped mountain in Tibet], 16
    - [Tibetan people by the side of a river], 17
    - [Tibetan people with their horses by the side of a river], 18
    - [Tibetan people climbing the side of a mountain in Tibet], 19
    - [Tibetan monks], 20
  - Tibet, 1949; 19 (Box 1582)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. receiving white cloth from a Tibetan monk (?)], 1
    - [Tibetan people climbing steep staris to the Potala Palace (?)], 2
    - [A Tibetan artifact in temple?], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. talking to Tibetan people on the side of a river in Tibet], 4
    - [Tibetan monks], 5
    - [Tibetan people dressed in yellow and red robes], 6
    - [Group of Tibetan people looking at Tibetan objects laid out on a mat], 7
    - [A ruined Tibetan home], 8
    - [Two Tibetan people dressed in colorful robes, standing outside of a Tibetan building], 9
    - [Tibetan children standing by a market in a Tibetan village], 10
    - [Tibetan vendor selling food?], 11
    - [Tibetan people on a street lined with trees in Tibet], 12
    - [A Tibetan man and two women with a baby in Tibet], 13
    - [Tibetan monks and officers walking alongside of a wall in Tibet], 14
    - [Tibetan people dressed in colorful costumes giving a performance in Tibet], 15
    - [Tibetan people climbing the side of a hill in Tibet], 16
    - [Group of people riding horses in Tibet], 17
    - [A ruined Tibetan house], 18
    - [Tibetan soldiers marching down a dirt road in Tibet with drums and flags], 19
    - [View of snowcapped mountains in Tibet], 20
    - [Tibetan oxen (yak?) carrying supplies across a field in Tibet], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 20 (Box 1582)
    - [A street in a Tibetan village], 1
    - [Tibetan monks], 2
    - [Young Tibetan monk with Lowell Thomas, Jr. in Tibet], 3
    - [Tibetan women burning something (?) on top of a hill], 4
    - [Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Sr. and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in Tibet], 5
    - [The Dai Lama in Tibet], 6
    - [Tibetan monk standing in front of a Tibetan building], 7
    - [Tibetan monks standing with Lowell Thomas, Jr. in Tibet], 8
    - [Pouring tea, in Tibet], 9
    - [Tibetan village], 10
    - [Tibetan people dressed in colorful robes, smiling, in Tibet], 11
    - [Tibetan artist painting], 12
    - [View of a Tibetan village in a valley in Tibet], 13
    - [View of snowcapped mountains in Tibet], 14
    - [Tibetan person holding their baby in front of a tent in Tibet, snowcapped mountain visible in the distance], 15
    - [A Tibetan farmer in Tibet], 16
  Box 1583
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Tibet, 1949; 1 (Box 1583)
    - [Lowell Thomas with Tibetan people on boat], 1
    - [Close-up of Lowell Thomas, Sr. and Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 2
    - [Tibetans riding on horses in Tibet], 3
    - [Men riding on horses in Tibet], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with a Tibetan monk, Potala Palace in background], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Sr. and some Tibetan people walking on a narrow dirt road in Tibet], 6
    - [Sun rising behind mountains in Tibet], 7
    - [Tibetan people in front of religious shrine in Tibet], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a horse on a stone path in Tibet], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas with some Tibetan people in front of horse-drawn carriage in Tibet], 10
    - [Lowel Thomas looking through a camera in Tibet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas listening to some people play Tibetan instruments in Tibet], 12
    - [Snowcapped mountains in the distance], 13
    - [Tibetan monks gathered], 14
    - [Monks walking down steps in Tibet], 15
    - [Tibetan monk on top of a Tibetan building], 16
    - [Tibetan monks and Lowell Thomas (?) on top of a Tibetan building], 17
    - [Three Tibetan women with a man in a suit, in Tibet], 18
    - [Tibetan people wearing bright red hats and purple robes, in Tibet], 19
    - [Tibetan monk using an instrument, in Tibet], 20
    - [Tibetan monks], 21
  - Tibet, 1949; 2 (Box 1583)
    - [Monks gathered in Tibet], 1